(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-26T22:23:21.275594",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
AZKi 8th Birthday Live
AZKi
AZKi 8th Birthday Live Cross Over 平成 vs 令和 アニソン歌合戦
AZKi 8th Birthday Live Cross Over: Heisei vs. Reiwa Anisong Battle
IRyS / 音乃瀬奏
IRyS / Otonose Kanata
みんなー！AZKiです！
Hello everyone! I'm AZKi!
今日は AZKi 8th Birthday Live CROSSOVER 平成vs令和 アニソン歌合戦にお越しいただき ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much for coming to AZKi 8th Birthday Live CROSSOVER: Heisei vs. Reiwa Anison Singing Contest!
今回は平成赤チームと令和青チームの2チームに分かれて アニソンで歌合戦をやっていきます！
This time, we're splitting into two teams—Heisei Red Team and Reiwa Blue Team—for an anime song singing battle!
今回ゲストのみんなもそれぞれのチームに分かれて 参戦してくれます！
Today's guests will also join in by splitting into their respective teams!
ハッシュタグは #AZKi生誕ライブ2026 こちらこちら！
The hashtag is #AZKi生誕ライブ2026, right over here!
で ぜひですね 赤チームここが良かったよとか 青チームここが美しかったよとかですね たくさんポストお願いします！
So please post lots of comments like "Red Team was great here" or "Blue Team was beautiful here"!
そして サムネイルにも書いてありますが 新衣装のお披露目と！重大告知もあるので 楽しみにしててくださーい！
And as written on the thumbnail, we'll reveal a new outfit! Plus, there's a big announcement, so please look forward to it!
ということで みんな 盛り上がる準備はいいかー！
So then, everyone, are you ready to get hyped?!
それでは 平成vs令和 アニソン歌合戦 開幕です！
Now then, let the Heisei vs. Reiwa Anison Singing Contest begin!
まずは平成赤チーム！
First up, the Heisei Red Team!
IRyS！
IRyS!
楽曲はアニメ『新世紀エヴァンゲリオン』より すべての始まりとなる1曲『残酷な天使のテーゼ』
The song, from the anime "Neon Genesis Evangelion," is the track where it all began: "A Cruel Angel's Thesis."
続いて令和青チーム！
Next, the Reiwa Blue Team!
音乃瀬奏！
Kanade Otonose!
楽曲は『シン・エヴァンゲリオン劇場版』より すべてを終わりに導く曲『One Last Kiss』
The song, from "Evangelion: 3.0+1.0 Thrice Upon a Time," is the track that brings it all to an end: "One Last Kiss."
時代を超えて交差する2つのメロディー 2曲続けてどうぞ！
Two melodies crossing over time. Please enjoy these two songs back-to-back!
残酷な天使のように 少年よ 神話になれ
Like a cruel angel, young boy, become a legend...
蒼い風がいま 胸のドアを叩いても
Even though clear blue winds beat on the door of my heart right now...
私だけをただ見つめて 微笑んでるあなた
...you just smile, looking straight at me.
そっとふれるもの もとめることに夢中で
Too absorbed in yearning for something softly touched...
運命さえまだ知らんない いたいけな瞳
...those innocent eyes still know nothing of fate.
だけどいつか気付くでしょう その背中には
But someday you will notice on those shoulders of yours...
遥か未来めざすための 羽根があること
...there are wings to guide you to the far future.
残酷な天使のテーゼ 窓辺からやがて飛び立つ
A cruel angel's thesis will someday fly high from the window.
ほとばしる熱いパトスで 思い出を裏切るなら
If memories are betrayed by the overflowing, burning pathos...
この宇宙を抱いて輝く 少年よ 神話になれ
...shine holding the sky in your arms, young boy, become a legend!
ずっと眠ってる 私の愛の揺りかご
Sleeping eternally in the cradle of my love,
あなただけが 夢の使者に呼ばれる朝がくる
The morning will come when you alone are called by a messenger of dreams.
細い首筋を 月あかりが映してる
The moonlight shines upon the nape of your slender neck.
世界中の時を止めて 閉じ込めたいけど
I want to stop time throughout the world and lock it away, but...
もしもふたり逢えたことに 意味があるなら
If there is meaning to the two of us meeting,
私はそう 自由を知るためのバイブル
Then I am a bible for learning what freedom is.
残酷な天使のテーゼ 悲しみが模そしてはじまる
A cruel angel's thesis, and so the sadness begins.
抱きしめた命のかたち その夢に目覚めたとき
The shape of life held close—when you awaken to that dream,
誰よりも光を放つ 少年よ神話になれ
Shining brighter than anyone else, young boy, become a legend!
人は愛をつむぎながら 歴史をつくる
People create history while weaving love together.
女神なんてなれないまま 私は生きる
Unable to ever become a goddess, I live on.
残酷な天使のテーゼ 窓辺からやがて飛び立つ
A cruel angel's thesis will soon take flight from the window.
ほとばしる熱いパトスで 思い出を裏切るなら
With surging, hot pathos, if you betray your memories,
この宇宙を抱いて輝く 少年よ神話になれ
Embracing this universe and shining bright, young boy, become a legend!
One Last Kiss
[Song: One Last Kiss]
初めてのルーブルは なんてことはなかったわ
My first visit to the Louvre was nothing special.
私だけのモナリザ もうとっくに出会ってたから
Because I had already met my very own Mona Lisa long ago.
初めてあなたを見た あの日動き出した歯車
The day I first saw you, the gears of fate began to turn.
止められない喪失の予感
An unstoppable premonition of loss.
もういっぱいあるけど
We already have so many,
もう一つ増やしましょう
But let's add one more.
Can you give me one last kiss?
忘れたくないこと
Something I don't want to forget...
Oh oh oh oh oh...
忘れたくないこと
Something I don't want to forget...
Oh oh oh oh oh...
I love you more than you'll ever know
「写真は苦手なんだ」 でもそんなものはいらないわ
"I'm not good at taking photos," but I don't need anything like that.
あなたが焼きついたまま 私の心のプロジェクター
You remain burned into the projector of my heart.
寂しくないふりしてた まぁ、そんなのお互い様か
I pretended I wasn't lonely, but well, I guess we were both doing that.
誰かを求めることは 即ち傷つくことだった
Wanting someone meant getting hurt.
Oh, can you give me one last kiss?
燃えるようなキスをしよう
Let me give you a burning kiss.
忘れたくても
Even if I try to forget,
忘れられないほど
It's unforgettable.
Oh oh oh oh oh...
I love you more than you'll ever know
もう分かっているよ
I already know
この世の終わりでも
even if it's the end of the world,
年をとっても
or even if I grow old,
忘れられない人
you're the one I can't forget.
Oh oh oh oh oh...
忘れられない人
The one I can't forget.
Oh oh oh oh oh...
I love you more than you'll ever know
忘れられない人
The one I can't forget.
Oh oh oh oh oh...
I love you more than you'll ever know
忘れられない人
The one I can't forget.
I love you more than you'll ever know
吹いていった風の後を
Chasing after the breeze
追いかけた 眩しい午後
that blew by on a dazzling afternoon.
AZKi 8th Birthday Live CROSSOVER
平成 赤チーム 常闇トワ
Heisei Red Team: Tokoyami Towa
楽曲は アニメ『けいおん!』より ガールズバンド旋風を巻き起こしたクールなロックナンバー 『Don't say "lazy"』
Her song is 'Don't say "lazy"', a cool rock number from the anime K-ON! that sparked the girls' band sensation.
続いて令和 青チーム
Next, the Reiwa Blue Team:
響咲リコナ
Hibiki Riona.
楽曲は アニメ『ぼっち・ざ・ろっく!』より 令和のバンドアニメの代表曲 『星座になれたら』
Her song is 'If I Could Be a Constellation', a flagship track of Reiwa band anime from 'Bocchi the Rock!'
時代を超えて響き渡るガールズバンドの系譜 2曲続けてどうぞ！
Enjoy two songs in a row showcasing the legacy of girls' bands transcending eras!
Please don't say "You are lazy" だって本当は crazy
Please don't say "You are lazy", 'cause the truth is I'm crazy.
白鳥たちはそう 見えないとこでバタ足するんです
Graceful swans flap their feet underwater where no one sees.
本能に忠実 翻弄も重々承知
Faithful to instinct, well aware of life's tricks,
前途洋々だし… だからたまに休憩しちゃうんです
my future is bright... so that's why I take breaks now and then.
この目でしっかり見定めて 行き先地図上マークして
I look closely with my own eyes and mark my destination on the map.
近道あればそれが王道 はしょれる翼もあれば上等
If there's a shortcut, that's the main path; wings that skip ahead are ideal.
ヤバ 爪割れた グルーで補修した それだけでなんか達成感
Oh no, my nail broke! Fixed it with glue, and now I feel accomplished.
大事なのは自分 かわいがること
The important thing is to treat yourself with care;
自分を愛さなきゃ 他人も愛せない
if you don't love yourself, you can't love others either.
Please don't say "You are lazy" だって本当は crazy
Please don't say "You are lazy", 'cause the truth is I'm crazy.
能ある鷹はそう 見えないとこにピック隠すんです
A skilled hawk hides its guitar pick where no one can see.
想像に一生懸命 現実絶体絶命
Pouring energy into imagination, while reality is a total desperate pinch.
発展途中だし… だから
Still a work in progress... so that's why
だから不意にピッチ外れるんです
That's why my pitch suddenly goes off...
その目に映らないくだって やる気はメーター振り切って
Just because you can't see it, doesn't mean I lack motivation; my meter's off the charts!
いつでも全力で夢見て その分全力で眠って
Always dreaming with all my might, and sleeping just as hard to make up for it!
ヤリ ちょい痩せた 調子づいて喰った
Yay! I lost a little weight, got carried away, and ate!
それだけでなんで？ 敗北感
Why do I feel such defeat just from that?
すかさずに目標 下方修正して
Instantly adjusting my targets downward,
柔軟に臨機応変 七変化が勝ち
being flexible and adaptable—adaptability wins!
Please don't say "You are lazy"
だって本当は crazy
'Cause in reality, I'm crazy.
孔雀たちはそう
Yeah, peacocks are like that too,
ここぞというとき美を魅せるんです
showing off their beauty when the moment is right.
五臓六腑 渾身 邁進
With every fiber of my being, pushing forward with all my power,
願望は痩身 麗人
my wish is to be a slim beauty.
誘惑多発だし…
There are so many temptations...
だからやけに意志砕けちゃうんです
That's why my willpower breaks so easily!
ヤバ まさか赤点！？ いや ギリクリア！
Oh no, a failing mark?! No, I barely passed!
それだけでなんて全能感
Why do I feel so omnipotent just from that?
大事なのは自分 認めてくこと
What's important is learning to accept yourself.
自分を許さなきゃ 他人も許せない
If you can't forgive yourself, you can't forgive others.
Please don't say "You are lazy"
だって本当は crazy
'Cause in reality, I'm crazy.
白鳥たちはそう
Swans are like that too,
見えないとこでバタ足するんです
paddling furiously underwater where you can't see.
本能に従順 忠実
Obedient and faithful to instinct,
翻弄も重々承知
fully aware of being tossed around by life.
前途洋々だし…
Our future is full of promise...
だからたまに休憩しちゃうんです
That's why we take a break once in a while!
もうすぐ時計は6時
The clock is almost turning six o'clock.
もうそこに一番星
The evening star is already up there.
影を踏んで 夜に紛れたくなる帰り道
Treading on shadows, wanting to melt into the night on my way home.
どんなに探してみても
No matter how hard I search,
一つしかない星
there is only one star.
何億光年 離れたところからあんなに輝く
Shining so brightly from billions of light-years away.
いいな 君は みんなから愛されて
How nice it is for you, being loved by everyone.
「いいや 僕はずっと一人きりさ」
"No, I've always been all alone."
君と集まって星座になれたら
If I could gather with you and become a constellation,
星降る夜 一瞬の願い事
On a night of falling stars, a fleeting wish.
きらめいて ゆらめいて 震えてるシグナル
Sparkling, wavering, a trembling signal.
君と集まって星座になれたら
If I could gather with you and become a constellation,
空見上げて 指を差されるような
Looking up at the sky, as if being pointed at...
つないだ線 解かないで
Don't undo the connected lines
僕がどんなに眩しくても
No matter how dazzling I may be
もうすぐ時計は8時
The clock will soon strike eight
夜空に満天の星
A sky full of stars in the night
何億光年 離れたところにはもうないかもしれない
Billions of light years away, they might not even be there anymore
月が綺麗で 泣きそうになるのは
The moon is so beautiful, and the reason I feel like crying
いつの日か 別れが来るから
Is because a farewell will come one day
君と集まって星座になれたら
If you and I could come together and become a constellation
彗星みたい 流れるひとりごと
Like a comet, a flowing soliloquy
消えていく 残像は 真夜中のプリズム
The fading afterimage is a midnight prism
君と集まって星座になれたら
If you and I could come together and become a constellation
切なる願い 誰かに届いたら
If an earnest wish reaches someone
変われるかな 夜の淵を
Wondering if I can change, tracing the edges of the night
なぞるような こんな僕でも
Even someone like me
遥か彼方 僕らは出会ってしまった
Far away, we happened to meet each other
カルマだから 何度も出会ってしまうよ
Because it's karma, we'll meet over and over again
雲の隙間で
In the gaps of the clouds
君と集まって星座になれたら
If you and I could come together and become a constellation
夜広げて 描こう絵空事
Spreading the night, let's draw an illusion
暗闇を 照らすような 満月じゃなくても
Even if it's not a full moon illuminating the darkness
だから集まって星座になりたい
That's why I want to gather and become a constellation
色とりどりの光 放つような
Like lights of various colors being emitted
つないだ線 解かないよ
I won't undo the connected lines
君がどんなに眩しくても
No matter how dazzling you may be
AZKi 8th Birthday Live CROSSOVER 平成 vs 令和 アニソン歌合戦
[AZKi 8th Birthday Live CROSSOVER: Heisei vs. Reiwa Anison Battle]
平成 赤チーム ロボ子さん
Heisei Red Team: Roboco-san
楽曲は アニメ『円盤皇女ワルキューレ』より 『Agape』
Song: "Agape" from the anime "UFO Ultramaiden Valkyrie"
続いて 令和 青チーム
Next up, Reiwa Blue Team.
水宮枢
Suu Mizumiya
楽曲は アニメ『うる星やつら』より 『トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ』
Song: "Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous" from the anime "Urusei Yatsura"
宇宙から届いた2つのラブソング 2曲続けてどうぞ！
Two love songs from space. Please enjoy them back-to-back!
Would you call me if you need my love?
どこにいたって聞こえる
No matter where I am, I can hear it
君がくれる Agape
The agape you give me
力の限り Dive!
Dive with all your might!
みつめる 触れあう その時
The moment we gaze and touch each other,
愛は 二人を 試している
Love is putting the two of us to the test.
Time is now
この世の果てまで
To the ends of this world
Would you call me if you need my love?
どこにいたって聞こえる
I can hear you no matter where you are
君がくれる Agape
The agape love you give me
力のかぎり Dive!
I'll dive with all my strength!
信じる 応える その瞬間
At the moment of believing and answering
愛が 僕らを ひとつにする
Love will make us one
Time is now
どこまでも生きて
Living on forever
Would you call me if you need my love?
どこにいたって聞こえる
I can hear you no matter where you are
君がくれる Agape
The agape love you give me
力のかぎり Dive!
I'll dive with all my strength!
Would you call me if you need my love?
どこにいたって聞こえる
I can hear you no matter where you are
君がくれる Agape
The agape love you give me
力のかぎり
With all my strength
Would you call me if you need my love?
どこにいたって聞こえる
I can hear you no matter where you are
君がくれる Agape
The agape love you give me
力のかぎり
With all my strength
Would you call me if you need my love?
どこにいたって聞こえる
I can hear you no matter where you are
君がくれる Agape
The agape love you give me
力のかぎり
With all my strength
Dive!
電波テンポアップして絶賛感電中！
Radio wave tempo speeding up, highly electrocuting!
あなたにもわすれたいことかなしいこと あるのかしらね
I wonder if you also have things you want to forget or sad memories
識らない映画なのに涙をながすのはドラマチックが足りていないからよ
Crying at a movie I don't know is because I lack drama in my life
そんな愚にも付かないことくだらないこと考えてばかりね
I'm always thinking about such silly and pointless things
雨が上がれば 愛もその横顔も 誰かのものになるのでしょう
When the rain stops, your love and that side profile will probably belong to someone else.
嘘っぱちのファンデーションも全部 今夜のためよ
All this fake foundation is all for tonight.
なのに一体全体如何にして如何して何故何故?
But why on earth, how, and why, why?
不安定なカンテラ何処まで行くの
Where is this unstable lantern heading?
あなた一切合切放り去ってもう
Throwing you completely away, already...
冗談じゃないわ トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ
I'm not joking around! Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous!
その時が来たって如何にもならないぜ
When that time comes, there's nothing you can do about it!
曖昧な本当なんてメランコリ化するだけ
The vague truth will only turn into melancholy.
あたしをさあ掻かっ攫って今テイクオンミー
So come on, snatch me away now, take on me.
はあ ちゃんちゃらおかしな法度ばっかで食指がびくともしないわ
Haa, with so many ridiculous rules, my appetite won't budge.
実態の無い感情放っておいたって策略なんてありゃあせんのに何故
Leaving behind baseless emotions when there's no strategy, why?
ああもう懲り懲りよ あたしの喝となる気質もじっと堪えて取り繕ってはとうとう臨界点
Ah, I've had enough! Holding back my fiery spirit, putting up a front, finally reaching the critical point!
年がら年中リップサービス鈍感かましては辟易
All year round lip service, acting insensitive, I'm sick of it!
どんガラガッシャンフィールガールは涙の目にも鬼
A tumbling feel girl is ruthless even to teary eyes!
今や頭の中のミュージックのせいであなたの話は一向に聴き取れない
Now because of the music in my head, I can't hear what you're saying at all!
少しは真当なこと言って
Say something sensible for once!
回り出すターンテーブル ねぇ全部忘れさせてよ
The spinning turntable... Hey, make me forget everything!
だけど一体全体如何にして如何して何故何故?
But why on earth, how, and why, why?
不安定なカンテラ消えないままね
The unstable lantern remains unextinguished.
あなた一口両舌食い違ってもう
You speak double-tongued, creating a rift, already...
冗談じゃないわ トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ
I'm not joking around! Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous!
その時が来たって如何にもならないぜ
When that time comes, there's nothing you can do about it!
曖昧な本当なんてメランコリ化するだけ
The vague truth will only turn into melancholy.
あたしを今...
Take me now...
冗談じゃないわ トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ
I'm not joking around! Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous!
その時が来たって如何にもならないぜ
When that time comes, there's nothing you can do about it!
不甲斐ないわ 感情なんてランドリーで落とすだけ
It's pathetic! Emotions are just something to wash away in the laundry.
あたしと確かめ合ってイエローマジック
Confirm it with me, Yellow Magic!
あーいやいや トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ
Ah, no, no! Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous!
その時が来たって如何にもならないぜ
When that time comes, there's nothing you can do about it!
曖昧な本当なんてメランコリ化するだけ
The vague truth will only turn into melancholy.
あたしをさあ掻かっ攫って今テイクオンミー
So come on, snatch me away now, take on me.
AZKi 8th Birthday Live Crossover! 最後はチームみんなで歌い上げます!
AZKi 8th Birthday Live Crossover! Finally, each team will sing together!
平成 赤チーム アニメ『とある科学の超電磁砲』より、未だ愛され続けるアニソンの王道、「only my railgun」!
Heisei Red Team! From the anime "A Certain Scientific Railgun", the timeless classic anime song: "only my railgun"!
続いて令和 青チーム アニメ『呪術廻戦』より、鮮烈でエモーショナルな青春ソング、「青のすみか」!
Next, Reiwa Blue Team! From the anime "Jujutsu Kaisen", a striking and emotional song of youth: "Where Our Blue Is"!
ステージでぶつかる電撃と呪力! 2曲続けて、どうぞ!
Electric shocks and cursed energy colliding on stage! Here are two songs back-to-back, enjoy!
放て! 心に刻んだ夢を 未来さえ置き去りにして
Release it! Engrave the dream into your heart, leaving even the future behind!
限界など知らない 意味無い!
Knowing no limits, they're meaningless!
この能力が光散らす その先に遥かな想いを
As this power scatters light, sending distant feelings far beyond!
歩いてきた この道を 振り返ることしか
I could only look back on this road I've walked...
出来ないなら... 今ここで全てを壊せる
If that's all I can do... then I can destroy everything right here and now!
暗闇に堕ちる街並み 人はどこまで立ち向かえるの?
In the cityscape falling into darkness, how far can people stand and fight?
加速するその痛みから 誰かをきっと守れるよ
From that accelerating pain, I can surely protect someone!
Looking! The blitz loop this planet to search way.
Only my RAILGUN can shoot it. 今すぐ
Only my RAILGUN can shoot it, right now!
身体中を 光の速さで
Coursing through my entire body at the speed of light!
At the speed of light, through my body,
駆け巡った 確かな予感
a certain prediction circulated.
掴め! 望むものなら残さず
Grab it! If there's something you wish for, leave nothing behind!
輝ける自分らしさで
We can shine with our own unique style.
信じてるよ あの日の誓いを
I believe in the vow from that day.
この瞳に光る涙
Even the tears shining in these eyes...
それさえも強さになるから
...will become my strength!
立ち止まると 少しだけ 感じる切なさに
When I stand still, I feel a slight sting of pain.
戸惑う事 無いなんて嘘はつかないよ
I won't lie and say I've never been confused.
宙に舞うコインが描く 放物線が決める運命
The parabola drawn by the coin dancing in midair decides my fate.
打ち出した答えが今日も 私の胸を駆け巡る
The answer it came to today circulates through my chest.
Sparkling! The shiny lights awake true desire.
Only my RAILGUN can shoot it. 必ず
Only my railgun can shoot it, without fail!
貫いていく 途惑うことなく
I'll pierce right through, without hesitation.
傷ついても 走り続ける
Even if I get hurt, I'll keep on running.
狙え! 凛と煌めく視線は 狂いなく闇を切り裂く
Aim! The glance sparkling coldly cuts through darkness flawlessly.
迷いなんて 吹き飛ばせばいい
We should just blast away any hesitation.
この心が叫ぶ限り 誰ひとり邪魔などさせない
As long as my heart screams out, I won't let anyone interfere!
儚く舞う 無数の願いは この両手に積もってゆく
Countless wishes flutter fleetingly, collecting in my hands.
切り裂く闇に見えてくるのは 重く深く 切ない記憶
Coming into view from shredded darkness are heavy, deep, painful memories.
色褪せてく 現実に揺れる 絶望には負けたくない
Shaken by this fading reality, I refuse to lose to despair!
私がいま 私であること 胸を張って 全て誇れる!
I'm proud of the fact that I am myself here and now!
Looking! The blitz loop this planet to search way.
Only my RAILGUN can shoot it. 今すぐ
Only my railgun can shoot it right now.
身体中を 光の速さで
At the speed of light, through my body,
駆け巡った 確かな予感
a certain prediction circulated.
放て! 心に刻んだ夢を
Release the dream engraved in your heart!
未来さえ置き去りにして
Leave even the future behind.
限界など知らない 意味無い!
I know no limits; they're meaningless!
この能力が光散らす その先に遥かな想いを
This power scatters light toward distant feelings beyond.
青のすみか
[Song: Where Our Blue Is]
どこまでも続くような青の季節は
This blue season of youth that seems to go on endlessly...
四つ並ぶ眼の前を遮るものは何もない
...has nothing to block the view before our four eyes.
アスファルト、蝉時雨を反射して
Reflecting the chorus of cicadas off the asphalt,
きみという沈黙が聞こえなくなる
the silence that is you becomes unheard.
この日々の色が褪せる
These days begin to lose their color.
僕と違うきみの匂いを知ってしまっても
Even if I've come to know your scent, so different from mine,
置き忘れてきた永遠の底に
at the bottom of eternity we left behind,
今でも青が澄んでいる
the blue remains clear even now.
どんな祈りも言葉も 近づけるのに、届かなかった
No prayer, no words could reach you, close as they got.
まるで、静かな恋のような
Just like a quiet love,
頬を伝った夏のような色の中
amidst the summery colors running down my cheek,
きみを呪う言葉がずっと喉の奥につかえてる
the words cursing you remain stuck deep in my throat.
「また会えるよね」って、声にならない声
"We'll meet again, right?"—in a voiceless voice.
昼下がり、じめつく風の季節は
On a humid afternoon, in the season of damp winds,
想い馳せる、まだ何者でもなかった僕らの肖像
I reminisce about portraits of us when we were still nobodies.
何もかも分かち合えたはずだった
We were supposed to be able to share everything.
あの日から少しずつ きみと違う僕という呪いが肥っていく
Since that day, the curse of being different from you grew bit by bit.
きみの笑顔の奥の憂いを
The sorrow deep within your smile—
見落としたこと、悔やみ尽くして
I regret with all my heart having overlooked it.
徒花と咲いて散っていくきみに さよなら
To you who bloom as a fruitless flower and scatter... goodbye.
今でも青が棲んでいる 今でも青は澄んでいる
Even now, the blue still lives on. Even now, the blue remains clear.
どんな祈りも言葉も 近づけるのに、届かなかった
No matter what prayers or words I spoke, I drew close, yet couldn't reach you.
まるで、静かな恋のような
Just like a quiet love,
頬を伝った夏のような色のなか
amidst colors like summer trickling down my cheek,
きみを呪う言葉がずっと喉の奥につかえてる
words cursing you remain stuck deep in my throat.
「また会えるよね」って、声にならない声
"We'll meet again, right?"—in a voiceless voice.
無限に膨張する銀河の星の粒のように
Like grains of stars in an infinitely expanding galaxy,
指の隙間を零れた
they slipped through the gaps in my fingers.
はい！ということで、ここまで一気にノンストップでお送りしました！
Alright! So, we've delivered everything non-stop up to this point!
いや、平成も令和も、いや名曲ばかりでしたね！
Wow, both the Heisei and Reiwa eras... it was non-stop classic hits, wasn't it?
どうでしたか？好きな曲はありましたか？
How was it? Were there any songs you liked?
そして、みんな、どっちのチームが良かったかな？
And everyone, which team do you think was better?
このね、今、後ろのこのハートのステージね
You see this heart stage behind me right now?
はい、こちらのハートに映し出された色で、どっちのチームが勝ったのか決まります！
Yes! The color displayed on this heart will decide which team won!
ぜひみんなコメントでどっちが良かったか教えてください！
Please let us know in the comments which team you thought was better!
えぇー？決められない？
Ehh? You can't decide?
いやいや、そこはね、ちょっとね、決めて... あ、すごい、この2色にね、分かれておりますけれども
No, no, you gotta choose... Oh wow, it's split cleanly into these two colors!
しっかり決めていただかないと。
But you really need to pick one for us!
はい、今日はね、あの平成VS令和となっております。
Yes, today is Heisei VS Reiwa!
はい！ということで勝ったのは、平成赤チームか？それとも令和青チームか？
Alright! So who won? Was it the Heisei Red Team? Or the Reiwa Blue Team?
一体どっちかな？それじゃあ行くよ？
Which one could it be? Alright, here we go!
さあ、結果はこちら！
Now, here are the results!
どっちかな？
Which team will it be?
ん？え？なんか紫になっちゃったんですけど！
Huh? Wait, it turned purple?!
紫って... 紫ってどっちですか？
Purple? What does purple mean?!
うーん... もうこれは、あの赤チームも良かったし青チームも良かったということで...
Hmm... Well, I guess this means both the Red Team and Blue Team were so great...
全てフュージョンして紫になってしまった！
...that everything fused together and turned purple!
ということで、いやみんな、たくさん歌ったし、みんな最高だったってことにします！
So since everyone sang so much and did their best, let me just say everyone was amazing!
いやなんか... みんなのおかげで、あ！なんかパワーが、パワーが溜まってきた気がするな！
I feel like... thanks to everyone, oh! I feel like power is building up inside me!
気がする！
I can feel it!
と言うことで、新衣装です！
And with that, here's my new outfit!
ピントが全部
The focus is all...
AZKiの魔力になっちゃった
...turned into AZKi's magic!
見てください どうですか？
Please look! How is it?
尻尾も 尻尾も生えてるんです
A tail... a tail grew, too!
フリ フリ フリ フリ
*wag wag wag wag*
どうですか？
How is it?
はい ということで今回は 小悪魔衣装をお仕立ていただきました！
Yes! So this time, I had a little devil outfit tailored for me!
どうでしょうか？ どうでしょうか？
What do you think? How is it?
魔力 魔王...
Magic power, demon lord...
小悪魔です
I'm a little devil!
はい 今回ですね 新衣装は こちらの小悪魔衣装 可愛いでしょう？
Yes! This time, my new outfit is... this little devil outfit! Cute, right?
今日たくさんスクショ撮ってくださいね！
Please take lots of screenshots today, okay?
ということで この衣装でね せっかくなので アニソンを歌っていきたいなと思います！
So, since I'm wearing this outfit, I'd like to sing an anime song!
もしかしたらね 小悪魔ですから この姿なら 魔法とかも使えちゃうんじゃないのかな？
Maybe, since I'm a little devil, in this form I can even use magic? Can I?
ということで ではですね 次の曲 聴いてください！
So then... please listen to the next song!
召喚ー！
Summoning~!
自分の過去に囚われ迷って
Trapped in my past and lost,
そうじゃないよと言い聞かせて 全てを
telling myself that's not true...
自由にあやつれるかなんて
"Can I control everything freely?"
分からないよと 空は霞んで 正解はどこ？
"I don't know," as the sky hazes over... Where is the answer?
僕の手のひらに 残る大事なもの
The precious thing that remains in the palm of my hand,
忘れない記憶 何度でも
an unforgettable memory... No matter how many times,
君を守り抜くと叫んで
I'll scream that I will protect you to the end.
巻き戻しの中 掴んだ愛はそう
The love I grasped within the rewind, yes,
離しはしないから
I will never let it go.
散りばめた思い 今一度きりの願いへ
Scattered feelings toward a one-time wish right now,
次への僕に 託したよ
I entrusted to the future me.
いつかの約束 光の道しるべになる
That promise someday will become a guiding light.
誓いをさあ君のため 最期まで
A vow, now, for your sake, until the very end.
涙さえ力に変えてきっと 描いていた望む未来へ 繋ぐよ
Turning even tears into strength, I will surely connect to the desired future I envisioned.
想像を超える事態に 狂って
Driven mad by a situation beyond imagination,
爪を立てては もがき足掻いて 心は
digging in my nails, struggling and squirming, my heart...
人生の過ちをもう何回
How many times must I repeat...
繰り返しては 嫌になって 泣いてても
...the mistakes of life, hating it and crying?
君の憧れは いつも輝いてた
Your ideal was always shining.
I'll come back To your future
僕は抗うだろう 運命に
I will fight against destiny.
Breaking out Breaking down
諦めちゃいないから
Because I haven't given up!
結ばれた意思は 独りきりじゃない強さへ
Bound determination leads toward a strength that isn't alone.
紡いだ糸を 手繰り寄せ
Pulling in the spun thread,
見つけた瞳は 理想を現実に変える
the eyes I found will turn ideals into reality.
世界はそう君のため 最初から
Yes, the world is for your sake, right from the beginning.
胸に抱いた思い出とずっと あの日から続く決意で
With the memories held in my heart and the resolve continuing from that day,
飛べるよ Redo
I can fly! Redo!
AZKiちゃん 生誕祭！ まだまだ行きますよー！
AZKi-chan's birthday concert! Let me hear you!
盛り上がっていこうー！
Let's get fired up!
君がたとえ僕のこと
Even if you...
忘れても 僕はもう忘れない 誰も傷つけない
...forget about me, I won't forget anymore, I won't hurt anyone.
消えそうな過去を 救い出すための時間よ
Oh time, meant for rescuing a fading past,
ここから始まれ
start from right here!
巡りゆく一瞬を 今一度きりの願いへ
A passing moment toward a one-time wish right now,
確かに僕は 託された
I was surely entrusted with it.
いつかの約束 光の道しるべになる
That promise someday will become a guiding light.
誓いを
A vow,
さあ 君のため
now, for your sake,
最期まで
until the very end,
涙さえ力に変えてきっと
I'll turn even my tears into strength and surely
描いていた望む未来へ
connect to the desired future I envisioned,
繋ぐよ
I'll link them!
はい！
Yeah!
ということで 来ていただいてありがとうございます！
So, thank you so much for coming today!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
今日は小悪魔衣装になって 魔法で召喚されちゃいました！
Today I put on a little devil outfit and got summoned with magic!
召喚されちゃいました！小あずき！
I was summoned! Ko-AZKi!
ありがとう！
Aw, thank you!
ということでね 皆さんもご存知だと思いますが
So, as I'm sure everyone already knows,
アニソン界のエース 鈴木このみさんに異世界転生してもらいました！
we had the ace of the anison world, Konomi Suzuki-san, reincarnate into our world!
召喚されましたー！
I was summoned!
誕生日をね 今日はお祝いしたいなと思って参りました！
I came here today wanting to celebrate your birthday!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
ということでですね 一緒に歌った曲は『Re:ゼロから始める異世界生活』の
So, the song we just sang together was from "Re:Zero - Starting Life in Another World,"
ファーストシーズンオープニングテーマ『Redo』でした！
the Season 1 opening theme, "Redo"!
いかがでしたか？
How was it?
ドキドキしたなー！
My heart was pounding!
いや 私もめっちゃドキドキした！
Mine was pounding like crazy too!
なんか『Redo』を人と歌ったことがあんまりなくて
I've rarely sung "Redo" with anyone else before,
あんまり怖い顔をして歌ってないかすごい心配です
so I was really worried if I was making a scary face while singing.
貴重な... 貴重な経験ありがとうございます！
Thank you for such a precious... precious experience!
AZKiちゃんと歌えて楽しかった！
It was so much fun singing with AZKi-chan!
「あずきち」って呼んでくれてるんですよ 皆さん！
She calls me "AZUkichi", everyone!
AZKiはね「このみん」って呼んでるんですけど
And AZKi calls her "Konomin"!
いや そう 実はね 出会いのきっかけはですね
Yeah, so actually, how we first met was...
いや もうずっとAZKiは元々大好きなんですけど
Well, AZKi has always loved her to begin with,
このみんがね あの『異世界かるてっと』の...
but Konomin was doing "Isekai Quartet"...
そうそう！『異世界かるてっと3』のエンディングテーマ...
Right, right! The ending theme for "Isekai Quartet 3"...
『キミイロボクイロ』のカルテットバージョンを作ることになりまして
We were making the quartet version of "Kimi-iro Boku-iro,"
で その時に会社の人から「誰か1人好きな人を召喚できる権利を差し上げます」って
and someone from my company said, "We'll grant you the right to summon one person you like!"
言われて...「はっ！そんな機会あるなら あずきちにお願いしてみたい」って
So I thought, "Ah! If I have that chance, I want to ask AZUkichi!"
私 ライブ元々見てたんで！
Because I'd been watching her live shows from the beginning!
えー！嬉しい！いいんですか？
Eh~! I'm so happy! Is that really okay?
いつかコラボしたいなーっていう気持ちがずっとあったので
I always had this feeling that I wanted to collaborate with her someday,
そこでラブコールをして 叶いまして！
so I sent her a love call, and it came true!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
まさかね そんなことがありまして
To think that happened, and from there...
そこからコラボ配信とか
...we did collaboration streams,
AZKiもね このみんのライブ見に行かせてもらったりとか
and AZKi even got to go watch Konomin's live concerts...
ありがとう！
Thank you!
あとはね ラーメンの...
And then, with ramen...
ラーメンのスープをね 飛ばしました！
We splashed ramen soup on ourselves!
配信の日にそういう話をしていて
We were talking about that on stream,
すぐLINEを交換して
and immediately exchanged LINE contacts,
すぐラーメンのスープを飛ばして
and immediately splashed ramen soup!
すぐそのあと焼肉にも行って
Right after that, we went for Korean BBQ,
油を飛ばして...
and splashed grease...
アフタヌーンティーにも行きました！
We also went for afternoon tea!
一応おしゃれなことも... 親しい... 結構ね！
We did stylish things too... we've gotten pretty close!
そうなんです！よく会ってるよね 最近！
That's right! We've been meeting up a lot lately, right?
なんと仲良くさせていただいております！
We've actually become really good friends!
濃厚なお付き合いをさせてもらっておりまして
We've been spending a lot of quality time together,
なんと今日！ついに！
and today, finally!
バーチャル空間に来てくれましたー！
She came into the virtual space!
初めてです！ありがとうー！
It's my first time! Thank you!
なんて楽しい空間なんだ！
What a fun space this is!
嬉しすぎるー！
I'm so happy!
嬉しい！なんかこの空間は魔法が使えるって聞いたんですけど 本当ですか？
I'm so happy! I heard you can use magic in this space, is that true?
使っちゃいます？このみんは一体どんな魔法を...
Wanna try using it? What kind of magic does Konomin...
私 も僭越ながら 1つだけ魔法を覚えてきたんですよ！
Humbly enough, I learned just one magic spell for today!
なんと！この日のために！これだけ使える！
What! For this day! This is the only one I can use!
これはでも みんなと一緒じゃないと完成しない魔法なんで
But this magic won't be complete unless everyone joins in,
ぜひあずきちへのラブを込めて
so with lots of love for AZUkichi,
何ですか？
What is it?
一緒に歌って魔法を完成させてください！
please sing along with me to complete the spell!
せーの！
Ready, set, go!
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday dear あずきち
Happy birthday dear AZUkichi
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
Happy birthday to you
あずきち 仕上げをお願いします！
AZUkichi, please do the finishing touch!
はい！ふーっ！
Okay!
このみんは炎の使い手でした！
Konomin was a flame wielder!
おめでとうございます！
Happy Birthday!
ありがとうございます！まさか歌までプレゼントしていただけるなんて...
Thank you so much! To think you'd even give me a song as a gift...
もう ここで命尽きても...
Ah, even if my life ends right here...
待って待って！ダメです！命尽きちゃダメなんです！
Wait, wait! No! You can't let your life end!
実は 皆さん 今日重大告知と...
Actually, everyone, today we have a major announcement and...
書いてあると思うんですけどね サムネに
I think it's already written on the thumbnail, though.
2人から重大告知がございます！
We have a major announcement from the two of us!
やったー！
Yay!
なんと！2人のオリジナルコラボ楽曲が出ます！
We're releasing an original collaboration song!
やったー！嬉しい！えー！いいんですか？
Yay! I'm so happy! Wow! Is this really happening?
ということでタイトルは... せーの！「最強未来衝動」！
So, the title is... ready, set, "Saikyou Mirai Shoudou"!
という なんだか強そうなタイトルですね 強い曲ですね！
That sounds like a powerful title. It's a high-energy song!
ということで なんと！今日 初披露させていただきます！
And today, we will be performing it for the very first time!
それでは早速聴いてもらえますか？
So without further ado, would you like to hear it?
それでは聴いてください！
Please enjoy!
だから JUST FLY TO THE STAR
So, JUST FLY TO THE STAR
もっと WOW WOW
More, WOW WOW
世界中で PROUDY GLOW
PROUDY GLOW all over the world
存在など 歌い切って 無い 無い
Sing until there's nothing left of our existence
壊れても 関係ない
Even if we break, it doesn't matter
そっと触れるよ 生まれたての星へ
Softly touching a newborn star
囁きながら 願い重ねた 宇宙
Whispering our overlapping wishes into the universe
ほどけた軌道は 誰も知らない場所へ
Unraveling orbits lead to an unknown place
微かな記憶と夢を この声に込めて
Pouring faint memories and dreams into this voice
今を 過去を
The present, the past...
未来を辿る
...tracing into the future.
一瞬を 一生を
A single moment, a whole lifetime...
この手で掴む
...grasping it with these hands!
超 BIG BANG!
Super BIG BANG!
ただこのまま果てまで
Just going like this to the end...
溶けちゃって
...melting away.
切り裂かれたような衝動
An impulse like being torn apart.
抱かれて 染まって 振り切って
Embraced, dyed, and breaking free!
まだ まだ ほら また
Not yet, not yet, see, once more...
星を 締め付ける
...constricting the stars.
君と絡まってみようか
Shall I become intertwined with you?
止まらないよ 最強未来衝動
It won't stop, the ultimate future impulse!
ただ ただ ただ ただ
Just, just, just, just...
剥がれ落ちてく
...peeling away and falling.
広がって 咲いて 駆け出して 飛んで
Spreading out, blooming, running forth, flying!
君と JUST FLY TO THE STAR
With you, JUST FLY TO THE STAR
もっと WOW WOW
More, WOW WOW
無重力で DREAMY SHOW
In zero gravity, a DREAMY SHOW
運命など 待ちきれない 無い
We can't wait for destiny, no, no!
壊れても 関係ない
Even if we break, it doesn't matter!
そっと祈るよ 幾千年の星へ
Softly praying to stars of thousands of years
彷徨いながら 僕ら出会えたんだ
While wandering, we managed to find each other
燃え尽きる前に 誰しも彼しも急ぐよ
Before burning out, everyone rushes on
確かな希望と信念を この声に込めて
Pouring certain hope and conviction into this voice
星よ 光れ
Oh star, shine bright
闇を照らせ
Illuminate the darkness
歌よ 響け
Oh song, resound
遥か彼方へ
Far into the distance
超 BIG BANG!
Super BIG BANG!
引力にさあ 導かれ
Guided now by gravity
この手を繋いだら
If we hold these hands together...
それだけでいい
...that is all we need.
聞いて! 鳴り止まない絶唱
Listen! An unending passionate song
愛して 焦がして 振り切って
Loving, yearning, breaking through
まだ まだ ほら また
Not yet, not yet, see, once more...
宇宙を 駆け巡る
...racing across the universe.
君を狂わせてみようか
Shall I drive you wild?
止まらないで 絶対未来衝動
Don't stop, absolute future impulse!
ただ ただ ただ ただ
Just, just, just, just...
生まれ落ちてく
...being born and falling.
そばにいて 触れて 輝いて 消えて
Stay by my side, touch me, shine bright, fade away
生きることは
Living is...
銀河を旅する STORY
...a STORY of traveling through the galaxy.
どこまでも 走っていく
Running forever onwards!
どこまでも 燃やしていく
Burning bright forever onwards!
どこまでも 生命がある限り
As long as there is life within us!
叫べ
Shout!
伝えたい この淡い衝動
I want to convey this faint impulse
伝えたい この熱い衝動を
I want to convey this burning impulse
I want to convey this passionate impulse
走れ
Run!
You can
ここから
From here,
次元を超えていく
we'll transcend dimensions.
超えていく
Transcending them,
超えていく...
transcending...
歌え！この衝動はきっと
Sing! This impulse will surely
抱かれて 染まって 振り切って
be embraced, dyed, and broken free of.
まだ まだ ほら
Not yet, not yet, look!
また 星を締め付ける
It grips the stars once again.
君と絡まってみようか
Shall we become intertwined with you?
止まらないよ 最強未来衝動
It won't stop—the ultimate future impulse.
ただ ただ ただ
Just, just, just...
剥がれ落ちていく
peeling away.
広がって 再生 駆け出して 飛んで
Spreading out, regenerating, running out, and flying!
だから JUST FLY TO THE STAR もっと WOW WOW
So JUST FLY TO THE STAR, even more WOW WOW!
世界中で PROUDY GLOW
PROUDLY GLOWing all over the world!
存在など言い切って無い 無い
There's no saying what existence even is, no, no!
壊れても関係ない
Even if it breaks, it doesn't matter!
はーい！ということで新曲を披露させていただきました！
Yay! And with that, we've just performed our new song!
ありがとうございました！
Thank you so much!
ありがとうございます！かっこいい曲になりましたね、このみん！
Thank you! It turned into such a cool song, Konomin!
えー曲！えー曲！
Such a great song! A great song!
ということでですね、「最強未来衝動」、本日この後7月2日0時からデジタルリリースされます！
So, "Saikyou Mirai Shoudou" will be released digitally starting at midnight today, July 2nd!
ちょっとせっかくなので...
Since we're here...
この曲、実は...
This song, actually...
2人で作詞を...
...the two of us wrote the lyrics...
そうなんですよ！
That's right!
いたしました！
...together!
2日間一緒に缶詰状態になって...
For two days, we were cooped up together...
部屋に閉じこもってね...
...locked inside a room...
このみんと一緒に作詞をするという、大変貴重な体験をさせていただきました。
...and I had a very valuable experience writing lyrics together with Konomin.
私もすごい楽しかったし、仲も深まったんじゃないかって...
For me too, it was so much fun, and I feel like our bond deepened...
そう！仲が深まったんじゃないか...
Yes! I feel like our bond deepened...
...気がしております。
...I really feel that way.
嬉しいです！そんな楽曲ですので、ぜひぜひ隅々まで聴いてほしいなと思います！
I'm so happy! Since it's a song like that, I really hope you listen to every detail!
お願いします！
Please do!
というわけで、今日はこの世界に来てくれてありがとうございました！
And so, thank you so much for coming to this world today!
ありがとうございました！どうでしたか？
Thank you so much! How was it?
正直言っていい？めっちゃ楽しい！
Can I be honest? It was super fun!
なんか巡動してる...
I feel so energized...
何でも炎とか出せちゃうんだって...
Like we could even shoot out flames and stuff...
そう、炎も出せちゃうし！
Yeah, we can shoot out flames!
最高！
Awesome!
最後に2人でこのハートマークを作りませんか？
At the end, shall the two of us make a heart shape together?
やりたーい！
I wanna do it!
じゃあ行くよ！せーの！
Alright, here we go! Ready, set...
はい！
...there!
いいんじゃないでしょうか！
Isn't this great?!
いいね！みんな撮れた？スクショお願いしますね。
Nice! Did everyone get it? Please take screenshots!
はい！ということでこのみんと一緒にハートを作ったところで...
Alright! Now that we've made a heart together with Konomin...
最後にこのみんから告知などありますか？ぜひ！
...finally, Konomin, do you have any announcements? Please!
はい！まず7月11日にアニサマ！
Yes! First, on July 11th, Anisama!
夏のアニメの祭典が行われます！
The summer anime festival will take place!
そちらに出ます！
I'll be performing there!
すごいすごいすごい！
Amazing, amazing, amazing!
フェスモードな感じで、アニソンですよね。
With a festival vibe, singing anime songs!
アチチな...
Super hot...
歌で炎バンバン出せたらいいなと...
I hope we can shoot out flames with our songs...
...思いますので、現実でも炎を出してくれます。
...so I'll make sure to bring the heat in reality too!
お願いします！
Please do!
あとはライブが決まってまして...
Also, I have a live concert coming up...
11月7日土曜日に東京SGCホールにて、「アニソンコレクションプラス」アニソンだけを歌うライブをやります！
...on Saturday, November 7th at Tokyo SGC Hall, "Anisong Collection Plus," where I'll only sing anime songs!
なんですってー！
What did you say?!
だから今日あずきちがアニソンずっと歌ってて...
So today AZKichi was singing anime songs all day...
そうなんです、今日アニソンをテーマにしたライブとなっております。
That's right, today's live is themed around anime songs.
ちょっと先取りじゃんって思いながら...
I was thinking, "Ah, she's doing it before me!"...
...ありがとうございます！
...thank you!
私もそんな1日を過ごそうかなと。
I plan to spend a day like that too.
応援してます！
I'm rooting for you!
代表曲ばっかり流れる、そんな...
It'll be packed with iconic songs...
そんなー、行かなきゃ！
No way, I gotta go!
ぜひ来てほしい！
I really want you to come!
行かなきゃ！ぜひぜひ！
I gotta go! Definitely!
ということで、詳しくはアカウントをチェックしていただいて、一緒にアニソンまみれの1日を過ごしましょう！
So please check my official account for details, and let's spend a day covered in anime songs together!
よろしくお願いします！
Thank you!
はい！ということで...
Alright! And so...
寂しいんですが、そろそろこのみんを元の世界に戻さないと、アニサマも...
It's sad, but I need to send Konomin back to her original world soon, or else Anisama...
...アニソンコレクションもできないので...
...and Anisong Collection won't happen either!
またご飯行こう！
Let's go eat out again!
ご飯行こう！
Let's go eat out!
行こう行こう！やったー！
Let me go, let's go! Yay!
じゃあ魔法を使ってこのみんを元の世界に戻したいと思います！今日はありがとうございました！
So I'll use magic to return Konomin to her original world! Thank you so much for today!
ありがとうございました！おめでとう！
Thank you so much! Congratulations!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
あー、消えちゃった...
Ah, she disappeared...
はい！ということでですね、サプライズスペシャルゲスト、鈴木このみさんに来ていただきました！
Alright! So, surprise special guest Konomi Suzuki came to join us!
今日のライブ、いかがでしたでしょうか！
How was today's live concert?!
豪華、本当にね、内容盛りだくさんで。
It was truly lavish and filled with content,
そうだ！
Oh right!
このね、新しい小悪魔な衣装のこと、あんまり話せなかったので、
I couldn't really talk much about this new little devil outfit earlier,
この後、メン限でゆっくり見てもらえたらと思います。
so I hope you'll take your time to look at it during the members-only stream after this.
実は、いろんなアクセサリーや差分があります！ということで、
Actually, there are various accessories and variations! So with that,
ぜひメン限もよろしくお願いします！
please look forward to the members-only stream as well!
そして、皆様！
And now, everyone!
最後に
Lastly,
AZKiから
AZKi has
みんなに
some happy news
嬉しいお知らせです！
to share with everyone!
こちらをどうぞー！
Please check this out!
傷ついた感情も 連れていくから
I'll take along these hurt emotions, too,
そっと響くファンファーレが 新しい未来を感じてる
as the softly echoing fanfare makes me feel a new future.
怖くたって 進むしかないでしょ 遠くまで
Even if I'm scared, I have no choice but to go forward, far away!
届くかな 祈りよ 光となれ
Will it reach? May my prayers turn into light,
もっと もっと 少しずつでもいい
more and more, even if it's little by little,
優しさという答えを
an answer called kindness.
もっと... もっと...
More... more...
お待たせしました！
Thank you for waiting!
AZKi Solo Live 2025『Departure』Blu-ray発売決定！
AZKi Solo Live 2025 "Departure" Blu-ray release confirmed!
開拓者のみんなと紡いだあのステージが
That stage we created together with all the Pioneers
何度でも見返せます！
can now be rewatched over and over again!
本日より受注受付が開始です！
Pre-orders start today!
続いて、告知2つ目！
Moving on to the second announcement!
AZKiの歴史を彩る
Coloring the history of AZKi,
EP2作品の再販が、本日7月1日より全国流通スタート！
the re-release of two EP albums begins nationwide distribution today, July 1st!
対象タイトルは『Without U』と『Re:Creating world』です！
The eligible titles are "Without U" and "Re:Creating world"!
最後！告知3つ目！
Finally, announcement number three!
AZKi誕生日記念2026グッズ情報！
AZKi Birthday Commemoration 2026 merchandise info!
今回はお披露目された小悪魔衣装にちなんだグッズが盛りだくさんです！
This time, there's a packed lineup of merch themed after the newly revealed little devil outfit!
イラストは信澤収先生に描いていただきました！
The illustrations were drawn by Nobusawa Osamu-sensei!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
それでは詳細を見ていきましょう！
Now, let's check out the details!
まずはこちら！
First up is this!
2層アクリルパネル！
2-Layer Acrylic Panel!
小悪魔衣装のキービジュアルをアクリルパネルにしました！
We turned the key visual of the little devil outfit into an acrylic panel!
2層になっているので立体的に見えます！
Because it's 2-layered, it looks three-dimensional!
ステンドグラスの神秘的な美しさと小悪魔衣装が見せるギャップを楽しんでください！
Please enjoy the contrast between the stained glass's mystical beauty and the little devil outfit!
続いてはこちら！
Next up is this!
ランダムラバーキーホルダー！
Random Rubber Keychain!
この後のメン限でも詳しく見せちゃうんですけど、
I'll show them in detail during the members-only stream after this,
今回の新衣装、実はバリエーションがいっぱいあるのでラバーキーホルダーにしてもらいました！
but this new outfit actually has lots of variations, so we turned them into rubber keychains!
君のお気に入りはどのAZKiかな？
Which AZKi is your favorite?
イラストは、にゃとら先生に描いていただきました！
The illustrations were drawn by Nyatora-sensei!
続いてはこちら！
Next up is this!
ぬいぐるみキーホルダー！
Plushie Keychain!
こちらも小悪魔衣装バージョンとなってます！
This one is also the little devil outfit version!
使い魔みたいなちゃめっ気のある表情になっているので、ぜひ相棒として連れ歩いてください！
It has a playful expression like a familiar, so please take it along as your companion!
続いてはこちら！
Next up is this!
おそろいブレスレット！
Matching Bracelet!
小悪魔衣装をモチーフにしたデザインのブレスレットです！
This bracelet design is themed after the little devil outfit!
日常の中でさりげなく推しを身に纏えるのはもちろん、
You can casually wear your favorite idol in daily life, of course,
普段アクセサリーをつけない方には新衣装の再現コレクションとしてもおすすめのグッズです！
and for those who don't usually wear accessories, it's also recommended as a replica item of the new outfit!
続いてはこちら！
Next up is this!
ASMRボイス！
ASMR Voice!
ボイスタイトルは『小悪魔チャーミング』！
The voice track title is "Little Devil Charming"!
AZKiが小悪魔っぽく魔法をかけちゃう？そんなもしものお話のASMRボイスです！
What if AZKi casts a spell like a little devil? It's an ASMR voice track of that "what if" story!
そして、フルセット購入特典もございます！
And there's also a Full Set Purchase Bonus!
信澤収先生イラストのAZKiのタロット風カードと特典ASMRボイスです！
It's an AZKi tarot-style card illustrated by Nobusawa Osamu-sensei and a bonus ASMR voice!
数量限定バージョンは、直筆サイン＆箔押し複製メッセージ入りです！
The limited quantity version comes with a handwritten signature & foil-stamped message copy!
通常バージョンは、箔押し複製サイン＆メッセージ入りです！
The standard version comes with a foil-stamped signature copy & message!
ということで、以上、嬉しいお知らせでした！
And so, that was all the happy announcements!
この後は、メン限でアンコールライブ！
After this, we'll have an encore live stream for members!
まだメン限に入っていない方も、まだ間に合うのでぜひ入ってみてください！
Even if you haven't joined the membership yet, there's still time, so please check it out!
実は今回の新衣装、みんなにまだ見せていないあんな姿やこんな姿があるので、見に来てくれたら嬉しいです！
Actually, for this new outfit, there are looks I haven't shown everyone yet, so I'd be happy if you came to see!
誕生日たくさんお祝いしてくれてありがとう！ライブも見てくれてありがとう！
Thank you so much for all the birthday wishes! Thank you for watching the live stream!
それじゃあ、この後メン限で会おうね！バイバイ！
Well then, see you in the members-only stream after this! Bye-bye!